♪ It seems today
that all you see ♪
♪ Is violence in movies
and sex on TV ♪
♪ But where are those
good old-fashioned values ♪
♪ On which we used to rely? ♪
♪ Lucky there's a family guy ♪
♪ Lucky there's a man
who positively can do ♪
♪ All the things that make us ♪
♪ Laugh and cry ♪
♪ He's... a...
Fam... ily... Guy! ♪
We now return
to Star Trek: Creep Space Nine.
♪ ♪
Ah! She saw us!
Warp speed!
Hey, you guys, you know
that song "Jimmy Crack Corn"?
Yeah, it's me and Lois'
wedding song-- what about it?
Well, the whole time the
guy's saying he doesn't care
that, uh, this Jimmy
fella cracked the corn,
but yet he wrote
an entire song about it.
Cared enough
to put pen to paper.
Are you on vacation?
I am.
Here's those fries you ordered.
And your hot sauce.
Hot sauce?
On fries?
Mm-hmm, oh, yeah.
Black guys put hot
sauce on everything,
on account of most of us
been pepper-sprayed
by the time we're two.
Can't taste nothing unless
you got that burn on there.
This stuff ain't that hot.
Whoo!
I feel like I'm crying,
but, like,
out of my neck and back.
Look at his face.
He looks like Oliver Platt
climbing a flight of stairs.
Hey! That's a low blow.
I'm gonna call the network
and complain.
Where's the phone?
It's upstairs, Oliver!
Eh, they know what they did.
Tell you what, Peter.
I'll give you ten
bucks if you drink
an entire shot glass
of that hot sauce.
Let me see the money.
You-you don't believe
I have ten dollars?
I think he's afraid.
Am not!
Prove it.
Ten bucks.
All right.
This is for all
the teachers who told me
I'd never amount to nothing.
Oh, my God!
That last one was more
caliente than hot.
But still, holy crap!
Well, here's your money.
This is awesome!
I can get people
to pay me ten bucks
just for doing stupid stuff?
Man, I haven't
made money this easy
since I invented the Yanket!
Peter, what's wrong?
Well, I want to masturbate,
but I'm just so darn cold.
Too bad there's no answer
for that problem.
But now there is.
Hi, I'm Peter Griffin,
creator of the Yanket.
If you're anything like me,
the number one problem
in your life
is that you can't masturbate
just anywhere.
But now you can.
Introducing the Yanket,
the only blanket
with built-in decoy arms.
Our patented process
makes it look like you're...
holding the remote
or sipping a beer.
Meanwhile, your real hands
are under the blanket,
going to town.
Peter, what are you doing?
Nothing. Let's watch
a Scarlett Johansson movie.
But wait, there's more!
We have Yankets
for all occasions:
Hey, what's going on
under that blanket?
You'll never know.
♪ ♪
All right, you guys.
I will now do anything
for ten dollars.
Who's got something for me?
I got one.
I'll give you ten bucks
if you wear the same pair
of underwear for a month.
Pay up.
Uh, actually, you owe me $20.
Ew. Here's $50,
go change your underwear.
It won't come off.
Hey, Peter, you want
to earn another ten bucks?
Course I do.
Great, I got a hilarious one.
I'll give you ten dollars
for your L4 vertebrae.
So, uh, I guess this means
Peter, you're our Joe now,
and Joe, you're our Peter.
That means you got to do
anything for ten bucks.
Okay.
I have a request.
Yay! Joe's chin!
Hey, Peter, I just
thought of something else
you could do for ten bucks.
Yeah, you know...
you know what?
I... I'm, uh,
think I'm gonna,
um, upping my price
to $12.50.
No, you ca...
no, you're locked in at ten.
Yeah, no renegotiating!
It was a joke.
Shut u... Just-just
point me to the thing.
All right, we're gonna open
this fire hydrant
and you're gonna drink as
much water from it as you can.
Chris has Crohn's disease.
Get down there.
Don't-don't-don't
tell us that now.
I think this is how
Anna Nicole Smith died.
Don't make light of that.
Holy crap!
We-we-we got to get out of here!
Aw, man, the library.
White Fang?
This is for ruining
my eighth grade summer!
He ruined my summer, too.
Oh, hey, Bri.
Still sitting in chairs, huh?
What'd your back
ever do to you?
I'm trying to watch.
Know what I'm watching?
My core.
Your body and mind are supposed
to be on the same team.
Sitting on the hard floor's
good for your back, too.
Coming up:
female high school teacher
sleeps with her students.
Is she hot? Stay tuned.
But first, the public library
suffered damage this evening
when an area fat man
smashed through
the front of the building
while attempting
a drunken stunt.
The bus station is expected
to absorb the overflow
of homeless
armpit-washing ladies.
Oh, God.
Peter, is there something
you want to tell me?
Uh, yeah, every light
in the house is on.
Did you destroy the library?
Did I destroy the library?
Ha, no, Lois.
That was television.
In light of events
at the library,
we now go live
to a press conference
at the mayor's residence.
Good evening, Quahog.
I'm here tonight
with the deputy mayor.
Hi, everybody!
Shut. Up.
Anyway, these types
of immature, drunken high jinks
are destroying our town.
And if we can't trust
a 42-year-old man
to drink responsibly,
then I have no choice
but to take action.
So, as mayor of Quahog,
I hereby raise the town's
legal drinking age to 50.
What?
I can't drink anymore?
What am I gonna do?
What do people do
who don't drink?
I don't know.
Knit?
Knit? Knit?!
Are you kidding me?!
Maybe.
Um, okay, so it turns out
I am, like,
crazy good at knitting.
Good afternoon, I'm Tom Tucker.
It's day three of Quahog's
new ban on alcohol
for anybody under 50.
And if there's one thing
the new drinking
age law has done,
it's let us know that women
tell terrible stories.
Good to see your
eyes open, Tom.
For more on this story,
we now go to Tricia Takanawa.
Tricia?
Joyce, I'm standing here
on the streets of Quahog,
where citizens are
feeling the effects
of the city's new drinking law.
I was going to bone
my girlfriend,
but she told me that if
there wasn't
vanilla vodka involved,
there was no way.
I think we just have to trust
our elected officials...
and Goldman's Pharmacy
is fully stocked on cough syrup,
which goes great
with ginger ale.
Well, I do miss drinking,
but I have used the time
to reconnect with my children
and I'm actually thinking about
resuming my actuarial practice.
Oh, my God, he's just
been drunk this whole time?
This new law sucks.
And I got to say,
it was kind of uncool
of Mayor West to call it
"Peter's Law."
No kidding.
Now I know how Megan
from "Megan's Law" felt.
I... I don't... I don't think
you know how she felt.
I don't know why I didn't
think of this before, guys.
We'll just go into the brewery
after hours and take some beer.
Hey, buddy.
It's okay, I work here.
Aren't you the guy who
cried in that meeting?
Oh, you know...
you know, I just remembered,
there's no beer here, l-let's-
let's just, let's just go.
Peter, why'd you want me
to get us into this prison?
Because, Joe, everyone
knows that all prisoners
make bootleg wine
in their toilet.
We are gonna get so wasted!
Oh! Look, right here.
This one's full of Chardonnay.
Peter, I don't think that's...
But it was Chardonnay.
The best Chardonnay
I'd ever had in my life.
The man who made it,
Curtis "Murder Dog" Williams,
went on to become
one of America's
most celebrated vintners.
Hey, Joe here.
Peter's lying.
He drank pee-pee.
Don't worry, guys.
If we can't buy
alcohol in Quahog,
we'll just go
to the next town over.
Sorry, in this town,
you can only buy alcohol
if you're dressed
head-to-toe in jeans.
What? Who made that law?
Our mayor, Jay Leno.
Have you seen
some of these laws
they've got now about denim?
You know, I say,
if you don't like it,
you may as well Levi's.
Who's voting for these mayors?
Rhode Island's a mess
from top to bottom.
I tell you, guys,
getting alcohol
when you're underage
isn't as easy as Obama's
daughters make it look.
What? Is that true?
I don't know.
Hey, isn't that
your dog at the bar?
Hey, Jerome, one more, neat.
What the hell?
Why's Jerome serving
booze to Brian?
I don't know,
but I'm gonna find out.
Come here, boy!
Come on!
Hey, what's up?
We going for a ride in the car?!
No, no, I had
a question for you.
Don't ever do that unless you
have a car ride to offer.
Hey, how come you're
allowed to drink?
Yeah, you're not 50.
Uh, actually, I am.
I'm 56 in dog years.
Oh, is that why you got
white pubic hair?
I'll thank you not
to check out my pubic hair.
Well, then don't go
flashing it around.
Put on some underpants,
you crazy old man.
Peter, I think
you're missing the point.
Brian can buy us booze.
Oh, my God, you're right!
W-Would you do that
for us, Brian?
Sure, why not?
Aw, thank God.
'Cause just sitting here
all sober
is more boring
than watching a pot boil.
Hey, you.
What are you doing?
I like to watch.
I want to watch you boil.
I can't do it
with you watching.
Oh, not even if I do this?
Don't do that...
Oh, God, that's so hot.
Oh, yeah?
Then why don't
I take your top off?
Oh! Oh...
I'm boiling!
Yeah.
Now I'm gonna stick
my raw pasta in you.
Peter, what's
going on in there?
Making dinner, babe.
♪ Brass Monkey ♪
♪ That funky monkey ♪
♪ Brass Monkey junkie ♪
♪ That funky monkey, Brass... ♪
♪ Got this dance
that's more than real ♪
♪ Drink Brass Monkey,
here's how you feel ♪
♪ You put your left leg down,
your right leg up ♪
♪ Tilt your head back,
let's finish the cup ♪
♪ MCA with the bottle ♪
♪ D rocks the can ♪
♪ Ad-Rock gets nice
with Charlie Chan ♪
♪ We're offered Moet ♪
♪ We don't mind Chivas ♪
♪ Wherever we go,
we bring the Monkey with us ♪
♪ Ad-Rock drinks three ♪
♪ Mike D is D ♪
♪ Double R foots the bill
most definitely ♪
♪ I drink Brass Monkey
and I rock well ♪
♪ I got a castle in Brooklyn,
that's where I dwell ♪
♪ Brass Monkey. ♪
Hey, hey, Brian, Brian.
How would you like to build,
build a deck right
now with your buddy?
'Cause we got hammers...
the whole deal.
I don't know, man.
It's pretty dark out.
That's okay.
I'll just pull my car around
and point the headlights at it.
Did you know that my dad
once called me a mistake?
That's messed up, man.
Wow.
You know, Brian,
hanging out with you
this past week has been awesome.
Yeah, why don't we,
why don't we do this anymore?
We-we-we used to do fun stuff
all the time, you know?
It used to be you and me.
And it always will be, pal.
Hey, listen, listen.
I want you to be
Meg's godfather.
No, thanks, Peter.
But this here,
we got to keep this going.
I agree, buddy, I agree.
All right, I'm gonna go barf
down the garbage disposal.
Brian, I think
we can get John Mayer
to stop tweeting again,
but we all got to work together.
Oh, my God!
Are you drunk again?
Yeah, I was, I was just hanging
out with my main man, Peter.
"Main man"?
"Hanging out"?
Brian, he's only using
you to buy alcohol!
What?
What are, wha...?
What are you,
what are you talking about?
It hasn't dawned on you
that he only started
spending time with you when
the drinking age was raised?
Come on, that's,
that's not true.
Aw, shoot, I puked
in the clean dishes side.
Trust me, as soon as you're
no longer of use to him,
he'll be done with you.
Oh, I get it, I get it.
Okay, you're, you're jealous
'cause I'm spending
all my time with Peter.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah, right.
Yeah, where's my dumb,
morbidly obese friend?
Hey, Stewie, get in here!
I'm being an '80s
computer hacker!
Come on, baby, show
me what you got.
And we... are in!
All right, I'd better go.
I got to go tell him
"This isn't a game, man."
Brian, do you have
any idea why Peter
was trying to climb
in the dishwasher?
I thought it was
a Tokyo apartment.
Sorry, Lois,
we, uh, we got--
I guess we had
a little too much to drink.
"To drink"?!
It's against the law
for him to do that!
Was Stewie in here?
Was, was he in here?
I... I smell his cologne.
Listen to me, Brian.
No more booze in this house.
You're gonna get us
all in trouble.
Peter, we--
maybe we should find
some place else to get--
to drink.
Yeah, I think you're right.
Hi, we're here
from the '80s FBI.
Somebody here
with a 2,400-baud modem
almost started World War III.
Oop, sounds like
they're making an escape.
Hey, you want to see me
run up that slide?
Sure.
Ow, damn it!
I think my belt buckle
cut my gut!
Hey, Peter,
can I ask you something?
You're not just hanging out
with me because I,
I can buy you alcohol, right?
What?! Course not.
We're friends.
Yeah, no, I-I know. That's,
that's, that's what I thought.
And also you bring
me dead birds.
I know Lois gets mad about it,
but I like using them
to point at things.
Hey, did they move the bagels?
Yeah, they're right there.
Oh, my God!
What the hell is that?!
This?
This is a pointing bird.
All right, I just saw
a sprinkler come on,
so I'm gonna go bite
at the water a little bit.
Hey, what's going on here?
Uh, some butthorn's
shining a flashlight on me.
I meant prior to me coming
up and investigating this.
Oh, well, you got
to be clearer, man.
I'm wasted.
Sir, I'm gonna
need to see some I.D.
You look underage.
Just as I suspected.
You're a minor.
It ain't my fault!
Somebody's been buying it
for me and all my friends!
Oh, is that right?
Well, you better
tell me who that is
or you're in a lot of trouble.
Hey, is this the park
where Boner died?
Wait, wha-what's going on?
That's him, Officer!
That's who's been
buying us the booze!
What?!
You get home, son.
You're lucky I'm letting
you off with a warning.
But you, you're coming with me.
You got to be kidding!
Do you need a ride?
Nah, I'm just gonna stay
here until the sun comes up
and then be the
best at tetherball.
Next!
What are you in for?
I bought some alcohol for
someone I thought was my friend.
How about you?
I threw a bottle of rum through
the window of the Apple Store.
I couldn't remember
me password.
Well, this sucks.
Oh, it's not so bad.
Sometimes they let you
take the good trash home
if you ask nice.
Last week, I got
an old greeting card.
It obviously wasn't for me,
but the imagination's
a hell of a thing.
Hey, Brian, what
time you get off?
Me and the guys were hoping you
could buy us some more beer.
You can't be serious.
Eh, it's a little bit serious.
Yeah, I haven't
been drunk in a day.
And I'm not feeling
particularly handsome.
Peter, you're
the reason I'm here!
You totally
sold me out to that cop!
Oh, are we just gonna
play the blame game?
'Cause I got another game
I'd rather play.
Boggle.
Go to hell!
You used me.
That's not what friends do.
It's what Adam Sandler's
friends do.
Now, if you'll excuse me, I've
got a half a can of hot beer
left in this open container
I've been driving around with.
You, too, pig.
Well, I'm not the
smartest man in the world,
but I can always look back on
my life and say I went for it.
Ugh, this seems like a weird
place to even use a condom.
Just shut up, Peter.
I'm done with you, all right?
You completely lied about why
you were hanging out with me.
What?
I never lie.
Well, except for that one time.
Oh, my God!
My husband's having
a heart attack!
Is anyone here a doctor?!
I have a 13-inch penis!
And besides, I'm sick of you
acting like you're
such a victim.
You agreed to buy us booze,
'cause we weren't old enough.
You're not old enough?!
You're a man in his 40s!
This whole law is ridiculous!
Hey, can one of you guys
with elbows
try to get this truck to honk?
Ah, that and giving noogies
is what I miss most
about having elbows.
You know, Brian,
what you said is right.
This law is stupid.
I mean, if it weren't for that,
we never would've
been in this fight.
Yeah, but what difference
does it make?
It's the law.
Nothing we can do about it.
The hell there's not.
I bet if we worked together
we could find a way
to change it back.
I... I don't know, Peter.
Come on, I know it seems hard,
but we can't just give up.
I mean, what if Thomas
Edison had given up?
Uh, what's that?
What's that thing
you're working on?
Well, it's a lightbulb and...
A lightbulb!
Lightbulb!
Yeah, I invented that.
Me-- I'm Thomas Edison.
I invented the lightbulb.
Uh, what's it do?
It lights up a room
using electrical...
Lights up a room using
electrical stuff!
I was about to say that,
because I invented it!
Uh, what are you working on?
It's a phonograph...
Phonograph!
I knew that,
'cause I invented it.
I'm Thomas Edison.
I rule!
♪ Look it up ♪
♪ Edison was a dick. ♪
Okay, Peter, I know how
we can get the law changed.
I've been doing some research,
and it says here
that in eight months, we can
get a non-binding proposition
on the ballot as long
as we get 4,000 signatures.
Ah, screw that,
we're going with plan B--
threaten to kill
the mayor's nephew.
I love you, Dad!
Peter, that's your son.
Shut up, Brian!
He's hugging me!
So, what exactly
is your plan, here?
You'll see.
Just follow my lead.
Ooh, trick-or-treaters!
Well, what do we have here?
A cowboy and a princess?
Uh, yippee-ki-yay, Mr. Mayor.
Oh, a Western princess!
All right, listen, we want
that drinking law gone.
And everybody knows the best way
to get any law struck down
is to get the gays
angry about it.
Bruce?
Jeffrey?
That's right,
Mr. Mayor!
I needs my Proseccos!
What are you talking about?
You're 52.
You said you was 39!
I was just trying
to get you in bed.
I thought we'd both
be dead by now.
Crap. But come on, you got
to change that law!
I mean, it's already
ruined a friendship
with one of the best guys
I know!
Adam, who's at the door?
Oh, hi, Brian.
Hi, Peter.
Wait a minute.
Is that, is that wine?
Yeah, Adam just poured me
a little before dinner.
Wow, you guys eat late.
No, Peter, don't you see?
Carol's underage, too!
The mayor just broke
his own law!
Hmm, that's a good point.
I guess I'll just have
to resign in scandal
while leaving the law intact.
Or you could
just change the law.
But it's a good law.
No, it ain't!
Look, don't you understand
what drinking
means to us working stiffs?
It helps us forget about our day
and tell our children we love
'em with a straight face.
It allows gross uggos to boof
each other's gross uggo parts.
And it gives people the courage
to sneak onto their mayor's
property and blackmail him
and eat all his ripe tomatoes.
That was a croquet ball.
Ah, then could you point me to
the closest nighttime dentist?
So listen, Mr. Mayor,
what do you say about that law?
All right, I'll repeal it.
But only if you send me and
Carol a copy of that picture.
We don't have a lot
of the two of us together.
Brian, we did it!
We got him to change the law!
Just goes to show, if anybody
wants a law changed,
they should just go
to their mayor's house.
Hey, I, uh, I-I appreciate
what you said there
about our friendship.
Well, to be honest, Brian,
at first I did just want you
to buy us beer.
But then the-the more
we were hanging out,
I-I remembered how much fun
we used to have together.
I guess after all these years,
I started taking you
for granted.
But you're still my best friend.
Even if I don't
always act like it.
I enjoyed hanging out
with you, too.
Thanks, Peter.
Hey, on your way out,
could you put this in my
mailbox for the mailman?
Uh, sure.
Put the flag up?
Of course put the flag up!
Geez, mail much?
Thank you for watching "Family Guy" on
www.FOX-fan.ru
Well, Peter, I'm just happy
that you and Brian
managed to get
that law repealed,
and that you're
finally friends again.
Me, too, Lois.
Good to have
my drinking buddy back.
Yay, everybody's happy!
I love this family!
I draped that over him.
He was just doing it
out in the open.